<Database>
	<!-- Plastic Surgery Mod by Sleepy068 -->
	<GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_EN_ADDON_PLASTICS_DIAGNOSES">
	<LanguageCode>en</LanguageCode>
	<LanguageNameLocalized>English</LanguageNameLocalized>
	<Contributors>
	<Name>Sleepy068</Name>
	</Contributors>

	<LocalizedStrings>
	
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_BREAST_01_V2</LocID>                         
			<Text>Breast Augmentation (C)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_BREAST_01_DESC</LocID>                         
			<Text>Breast Augmentation, also known as augmentation mammoplasty, can be a cosmetic (C) procedure or a reconstructive (R) procedure in the case of breast reconstruction surgery. The procedure involves implants being inserted beneath the breasts to enlarge them. The implant type and size depends on factors such as how much bigger the patient wants their breasts to be, their breast anatomy, skin thickness and elasticity, and body type. The patient has expressed that they want a Cosmetic Breast Augmentation to enhance their appearance.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_STOMACH_01_V2</LocID>                         
			<Text>Liposuction (C)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_STOMACH_01_DESC</LocID>                         
			<Text>Liposuction, also known as lipectomy or lipoplasty, is a procedure that improves the body’s contours and proportion by removing excess fat deposits to slim and reshape specific areas of the body. Common areas targeted include thighs, buttocks, abdomen, arms, neck and under the chin. Usually liposuction of smaller volumes are done as an outpatient while larger volumes require a stay in hospital to monitor fluid levels and if patients are suffering from any other medical conditions. The patient has expressed that they want a Liposuction to enhance their appearance.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_NOSE_01_V2</LocID>                         
			<Text>Augmentation Rhinoplasty (C)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_NOSE_01_DESC</LocID>                         
			<Text>Augmentation Rhinoplasty is surgery that changes the shape of the nose. The motivation for rhinoplasty may be to change the appearance of the nose, improve breathing or both. Augmentation Rhinoplasty is commonly referred to as a “nose job". This surgical procedure works to enhance the outward look of the nose, or its external aesthetics. This often involves reshaping a “crooked” nose or bringing a large nose into better proportion with the rest of the face.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_R_EYE_01</LocID>                         
			<Text>Blepharospasm (R)(Mild)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_R_EYE_01_DESC</LocID>                         
			<Text>Blepharospasm is abnormal contraction of the eyelid muscles. It often refers to benign essential blepharospasm (BEB) which is a bilateral condition and a form of focal dystonia leading to episodic closure of the eyelids. In more mild cases, Botulinum Toxin injections is a commonly accepted treatment. It takes between one and four days for the paralysis to begin. The complete effect usually takes about a week and often lasts up to four months.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_R_EYE_02_V2</LocID>                         
			<Text>Strabismus (R)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_R_EYE_02_DESC</LocID>                         
			<Text>Strabismus is a condition in which the eyes do not properly align with each other when looking at an object. The eye that is focused on an object can alternate. The condition may be present occasionally or constantly. If present during a large part of childhood, it may result in amblyopia or loss of depth perception. Although it is often considered a childhood condition, the incidence of strabismus is actually higher in adults.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_HAIR_01_V2</LocID>                         
			<Text>Hair Transplant (C)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_HAIR_01_DESC</LocID>                         
			<Text>Hair transplantation is a surgical technique that removes hair follicles from one part of the body, called the 'donor site', to a bald or balding part of the body known as the 'recipient site'. The technique is primarily used to treat male pattern baldness. In this minimally invasive procedure, grafts containing hair follicles that are genetically resistant to balding (like the back of the head) are transplanted to the bald scalp. Hair transplantation can also be used to restore eyelashes, eyebrows, beard hair, chest hair, pubic hair and to fill in scars caused by accidents or surgery such as face-lifts and previous hair transplants.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_SKIN_01</LocID>                         
			<Text>Chemical Peel (Light Peel)(C)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_SKIN_01_DESC</LocID>                         
			<Text>Chemical peel is a form of treatment that uses chemical solutions to correct facial blemishes, wrinkles and uneven skin pigmentation. In this treatment, a chemical solution is applied to the skin, which makes it "blister" and eventually peel off. The new skin is usually smoother and less wrinkled than the old skin.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_R_VEIN_01</LocID>                         
			<Text>Varicose Veins (Simple)(R)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_R_VEIN_01_DESC</LocID>                         
			<Text>Varicose veins are twisted, enlarged veins. Any superficial vein may become varicosed, but the veins most commonly affected are those in the legs. For many patients, varicose veins are simply a cosmetic concern. For other patients, varicose veins can cause aching pain and discomfort and may lead to more-serious problems.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_VEIN_01</LocID>                         
			<Text>Telangiectasias (C)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_VEIN_01_DESC</LocID>                         
			<Text>Telangiectasias, commonly know as Spider Veins are clusters of tiny blood vessels that develop close to the surface of the skin. They are often red, blue, or purple; and they have the appearance of a spiderweb. They are commonly found on the face and legs.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_R_HAND_01_M</LocID>                         
			<Text>Dupuytren’s Contracture (Simple)(R)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_R_HAND_01_F</LocID>                         
			<Text>Dupuytren’s Contracture (Simple)(R)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_R_HAND_01_DESC</LocID>                         
			<Text>Dupuytren contracture, also know as palmar fibromatosis, is characterised by a deformity of the hand in which the joints of one or more fingers cannot be fully straightened, it usually develops over years. The condition affects a layer of tissue that lies under the skin of your palm. Knots of tissue form under the skin — eventually creating a thick cord that can pull one or more fingers into a bent position. When simple, the condition can be relatively easy to correct without needing surgical intervention.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_R_SCAR_01</LocID>                         
			<Text>Hypertrophic Scar (Simple)(R)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_R_SCAR_01_DESC</LocID>                         
			<Text>A hypertrophic scar is a thickened, wide, often raised scar that develops where skin is injured. Scars are common during the wound healing process, but a hypertrophic scar is a result of an abnormal response to a trauma or injury. The scars are a frequent complication of burn injuries, but can also form after piercings, cuts, or even acne. Hypertrophic scars are similar to keloid scars but tend to be milder and don’t grow beyond the boundaries of the original skin injury. The scars aren’t dangerous or life-threatening. They can be itchy and painful, but more often are simply a cosmetic issue.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_R_SCAR_02</LocID>                         
			<Text>Keloid Scar (Simple)(R)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_R_SCAR_02_DESC</LocID>                         
			<Text>Keloids are a type of raised scar. They occur where the skin has healed after an injury. They can grow to be much larger than the original injury that caused the scar. Anything that can cause a scar can cause a keloid. This includes being burned, cut, or having severe acne. </Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_R_T_REPLANT_01_V2</LocID>                         
			<Text>Amputated Digit (GT)(R)(HB)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_R_T_REPLANT_01_DESC</LocID>                         
			<Text>Traumatic amputation is the loss of a body part that occurs as the result of an accident or injury. In this case, a digit on the patient's hand has been amputated and requires immediate medical attention to attempt to restore function to the hand and digit. Sharp, guillotine-type (GT) injuries with relatively uninjured surrounding tissue have the best post-replantation prognosis, with a success rate of 77%. Severe crush injuries (CI), multi-level injuries, and avulsion injuries often mangle soft tissue to the point of precluding rejoining of essential blood vessels, making replantation impossible. In such cases, revision amputation of the stump may be necessary. The patient has arrived to the hospital with the severed body part (HB).</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_SKIN_02</LocID>                         
			<Text>Skin Conditioning (Botulinum Toxin Therapy)(C)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_SKIN_02_DESC</LocID>                         
			<Text>Botox injections are noted primarily for the ability to reduce the appearance of facial wrinkles. Botox injections block certain chemical signals from nerves, mostly signals that cause muscles to contract. The most common use of these injections is to temporarily relax the facial muscles that cause wrinkles in the forehead and around the eyes.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_SKIN_03</LocID>                         
			<Text>Skin Conditioning (Dermal Fillers)(C)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_SKIN_03_DESC</LocID>                         
			<Text>Dermal fillers, sometimes called soft tissue fillers, are materials injected under the skin to reduce the appearance of facial wrinkles or lines, and can also be used to enhance facial contours by adding volume to cheeks and lips and to improve the appearance of scars. Dermal filler products are biodegradable, which means they will naturally disappear in the body. The longevity of the filler can vary, depending on the brand, thickness and area treated.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_SKIN_04</LocID>                         
			<Text>Skin Rejuvenation (Laser Resurfacing)(C)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_SKIN_04_DESC</LocID>                         
			<Text>Laser resurfacing is a facial rejuvenation procedure that uses a laser to improve the skin's appearance or treat minor facial flaws. Laser resurfacing can decrease the appearance of fine lines in the face. It can also treat loss of skin tone and improve the patient's complexion if they have scars or sun damage. Laser resurfacing can't eliminate excessive or sagging skin.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
	<!-- ================================================== -->
	<!-- ============= Plastic Surgery v1.0.6 ============= -->
	<!-- ================================================== -->
	
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_BREAST_02</LocID>                         
			<Text>Breast Lift (Mastopexy)C)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_BREAST_02_DESC</LocID>                         
			<Text>Breast lift, also known as mastopexy, is a procedure that raises and firms the breasts. The surgical procedure also reshapes the nipple-areola complex and lifts the breasts on the chest wall. The patient has expressed that they want a Breast Lift to enhance their appearance.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_NOSE_02</LocID>                         
			<Text>Septoplasty (C)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_NOSE_02_DESC</LocID>                         
			<Text>Septoplasty, or septal reconstruction, is a corrective surgical procedure done to straighten a deviated nasal septum – the nasal septum being the partition between the two nasal cavities. Ideally, the septum should run down the centre of the nose. The patient has expressed that they want a Septoplasty to enhance their appearance.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_R_T_REPLANT_02</LocID>                         
			<Text>Amputated Toe (GT)(R)(HB)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_R_T_REPLANT_02_DESC</LocID>                         
			<Text>Traumatic amputation is the loss of a body part that occurs as the result of an accident or injury. In this case, a toe on the patient's foot has been amputated and requires immediate medical attention to attempt to restore function to the foot and toe. Sharp, guillotine-type (GT) injuries with relatively uninjured surrounding tissue have the best post-replantation prognosis, with a success rate of 77%. Severe crush injuries (CI), multi-level injuries, and avulsion injuries often mangle soft tissue to the point of precluding rejoining of essential blood vessels, making replantation impossible. In such cases, revision amputation of the stump may be necessary. The patient has arrived to the hospital with the severed body part (HB).</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_R_NOSE_01</LocID>                         
			<Text>Nasal Deformities</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_R_NOSE_01_DESC</LocID>                         
			<Text>The patient's nose has structural defects that are causing issues both aesthetically and functionally.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_CHECKUP_01</LocID>                         
			<Text>Checkup: Breast Augmentation (C)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_CHECKUP_01_DESC</LocID>                         
			<Text>The patient has a follow up appointment with their doctor. The patient is following up a recent Breast Augmentation surgery and the doctor will check the wound, replace any dressings and remove any stitches, staples, adhesives or drains that are still in place if necessary.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_CHECKUP_02</LocID>                         
			<Text>Checkup: Augmentation Rhinoplasty (C)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_CHECKUP_02_DESC</LocID>                         
			<Text>The patient has a follow up appointment with their doctor. The patient is following up a recent Augmentation Rhinoplasty surgery and the doctor will check the wound, replace any dressings and remove any stitches, staples, adhesives or drains that are still in place if necessary.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_CHECKUP_03</LocID>                         
			<Text>Checkup: Liposuction (C)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_CHECKUP_03_DESC</LocID>                         
			<Text>The patient has a follow up appointment with their doctor. The patient is following up a recent Liposuction surgery and the doctor will check the wound, replace any dressings and remove any stitches, staples, adhesives or drains that are still in place if necessary.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_R_T_BLAST_01</LocID>                         
			<Text>Blast-related Ocular Trauma (Irreparable) </Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_R_T_BLAST_01_DESC</LocID>                         
			<Text>Blast-related ocular trauma comprises a specialised group of penetrating and blunt force injuries to the eye and its structure caused by the detonation of explosive materials. The patients eye is all but obliterated making recovery impossible and the situation critical. Emergency care and surgery will be required to prevent any further blood loss, infections and damage to surrounding tissue. </Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_CHECKUP_04</LocID>                         
			<Text>Checkup: Mastopexy (C)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_CHECKUP_04_DESC</LocID>                         
			<Text>The patient has a follow up appointment with their doctor. The patient is following up a recent Mastopexy surgery and the doctor will check the wound, replace any dressings and remove any stitches, staples, adhesives or drains that are still in place if necessary.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_CHECKUP_05</LocID>                         
			<Text>Checkup: Septoplasty (C)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>DIA_PLAS_C_CHECKUP_05_DESC</LocID>                         
			<Text>The patient has a follow up appointment with their doctor. The patient is following up a recent Septoplasty surgery and the doctor will check the wound, replace any dressings and remove any stitches, staples, adhesives or drains that are still in place if necessary.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		
		<!--
		Translators, please ignore this:
		Used to quickly add new localisation to the mod 
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>XYZ</LocID>                         
			<Text></Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
			<LocID>XYZ_DESC</LocID>                         
			<Text></Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		-->
	</LocalizedStrings>
	</GameDBStringTable>
</Database>

