<Database>
	<!-- Plastic Surgery Mod by Sleepy068 -->
	<GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_EN_ADDON_PLASTICS_SYMPTOMS">
	<LanguageCode>en</LanguageCode>
	<LanguageNameLocalized>English</LanguageNameLocalized>
	<Contributors>
	<Name>Sleepy068</Name>
	</Contributors>

	<LocalizedStrings>
	<!-- =========================================== -->
	<!-- ============= Plastic Surgery ============= -->
	<!-- =========================================== -->
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_PLAS_NERVE_DAMAGE_V2</LocID>                               
		<Text>Postoperative Neuropathic Pain</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_PLAS_NERVE_DAMAGE_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>Postoperative neuropathic pain (PONP) can develop if nerves were damaged during a surgery. Damaged nerves cannot correctly transmit signals from various parts of the body to the brain. Instead, these signals become exaggerated, causing chronic pain that may persist for months or even years.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_UNDESIRED_RESULTS_V2</LocID>                               
		<Text>Undesired Results</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_UNDESIRED_RESULTS_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>Unfavourable outcomes are part and parcel of performing surgeries of any kind. Post-treatment undesired results occur after a surgery or treatment has been completed and the result differs from what was expected. This may lead to further complications and increased stress for the patient.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_S_SCAR_TISSUE_V2</LocID>                               
		<Text>Significant Scar Tissue</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_S_SCAR_TISSUE_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>A scar is a mark that is left on the skin after a wound or an injury to the surface of the skin has healed. The formation of scars or scar tissue is a normal part of the healing process, and occurs when the skin is cut due to injury or surgery. The growth of scar tissue is influenced by many factors, these include: The severity of the original injury. The size, depth and location of the wound on the body. Excess scar tissue, layers deep, can significantly reduce function and movement months after surgery. This can have negative effects and decrease patient satisfaction.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_B_CAPSULAR_V2</LocID>                               
		<Text>Capsular Contracture</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_B_CAPSULAR_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>Capsular contracture is a breast augmentation complication that develops when internal scar tissue forms a tight or constricting capsule around a breast implant, contracting it until it becomes misshapen and hard.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_BARSA_INFECTION_V2</LocID>                               
		<Text>Breast Implant Infection</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_BARSA_INFECTION_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>At face value, bacterial infection is a problem for any implantable medical device, including breast implants. Symptoms of an infection can include a high fever and breast pain, redness and/or swelling. If it appears that antibiotics alone won't clear the infection, then the surgeon may need to clean out the infected tissue and either replace or completely remove the implant.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_FAILED_BA_V2</LocID>                               
		<Text>Failed Breast Augmentation</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_FAILED_BA_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>Due to surgery complications, the patient has been unable to have a successful cosmetic surgery outcome. They will not be happy about this. </Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_B_IMPLANT_EXTRUSION_V2</LocID>                               
		<Text>Breast Implant Extrusion</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_B_IMPLANT_EXTRUSION_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>In relatively rare cases after implant reconstruction surgery, the surface of the implant or tissue expander comes through the skin and becomes exposed. This is called “extrusion". The patient may develop an infection if they have an extruded or exposed implant. If the breast implant has already extruded or is about to extrude, the plastic surgeon will have to remove it or replace it via corrective surgery.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_PLAS_ABSCESS</LocID>                   
		<Text>Abscess</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_NOSE_SEPTALPERF_V2</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Nasal Septal Perforation</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_NOSE_SEPTALPERF_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>A nasal septum perforation is a medical condition in which the nasal septum, the bony/cartilaginous wall dividing the nasal cavities, develops a hole or fissure. Some perforations can cause bleeding, pain, and a whistling sound when inhaling. If dried blood or scabs build up, you could also have trouble breathing through your nose. Many perforations do not need to be closed but serious or complicated ones can lead to infections.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_EYE_GLOBE_PERFORATION_V2</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Globe Perforation</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_EYE_GLOBE_PERFORATION_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>Globe rupture occurs when the integrity of the outer membranes of the eye is disrupted by blunt or penetrating trauma. Any full-thickness injury to the cornea, sclera, or both is considered an open globe injury and is approached in the same manner in the acute setting. Globe rupture is an ophthalmologic emergency and prompt action is critical to maximizing functional outcome. Although the globe's position within the orbit protects it from injury in many situations, damage to the posterior segment of the eye is associated with a very high frequency of permanent visual loss.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_EYE_UNDESIRED_RESULTS_V2</LocID>                                          	
		<Text>Unsatisfactory Eye Alignment</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_EYE_UNDESIRED_RESULTS_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>Unsatisfactory eye alignment after surgery is the most common complication when correcting Strabismus and other eye misalignment issues. Despite careful pre-operative measurements and utilization of common surgical dosage tables, a certain percentage of patients will be overcorrected or undercorrected after surgery requiring corrective surgical procedures to alleviate the issue.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_EYE_CIC_V2</LocID>                               
		<Text>Conjunctival Inclusion Cyst</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_EYE_CIC_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>Conjunctival inclusion cysts occur when conjunctival epithelial cells are buried beneath the conjunctival surface during surgery. These cells can multiply over time to create a subconjunctival cyst days to years after the original surgery. Conjunctival scaring is more common after a re-operation and also after a surgical resection, when advancement of the muscle belly may advance the thicker posterior Tenon’s capsule closer to the limbus where it is more visible.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_EYE_SLIPPED_MUSCLE_V2</LocID>                               
		<Text>Slipped Muscle</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_EYE_SLIPPED_MUSCLE_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>Slipped muscles develop when the muscular capsule is imbricated without including the muscle or muscle tendon during strabismus surgery. When the capsule is reattached to the sclera, the tendon and muscle are then free to slip posteriorally from the site of attachment.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<!-- ================================================== -->
	<!-- ============= Plastic Surgery v1.0.6 ============= -->
	<!-- ================================================== -->
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_CSFRHINORRHEA</LocID>                         
		<Text>Cerebrospinal Fluid (CSF) Rhinorrhea</Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_CSFRHINORRHEA_DESC</LocID>                         
		<Text>Cerebrospinal fluid (CSF) rhinorrhea is a condition where the fluid that surrounds the brain leaks into the nose and sinuses. Head trauma, surgery, or even birth defects can make a hole in the membranes that hold this fluid. It then leaks into the nose or ear, causing a watery, runny nose.</Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString> <!-- NOT FOR CRP -->     
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_NASAL_HEMATOMA</LocID>                         
		<Text>Nasal Hematoma</Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString> <!-- NOT FOR CRP -->  
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_NASAL_HEMATOMA_DESC</LocID>                         
		<Text>A nasal septal hematoma is a collection of blood within the septum of the nose. The septum is the part of the nose between the nostrils. An injury disrupts the blood vessels so that fluid and blood may collect under the lining.</Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_LOW_NOSEBRIDGE</LocID>                         
		<Text>Very Low Nose Bridge</Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_LOW_NOSEBRIDGE_DESC</LocID>                         
		<Text>The patient has an exceptionally low nasal bridge. This can cause issues concerning the functionality of the nose.</Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_DISPROPORT_APPEAR</LocID>                         
		<Text>Disproportionate Appearance (Nose)</Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_DISPROPORT_APPEAR_DESC</LocID>                         
		<Text>The appearance and size of the patient's nose is noticeably difference from what would be considered normal.</Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_PINCHED_NOSTRILS</LocID>                         
		<Text>Pinched Nostrils</Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_PINCHED_NOSTRILS_DESC</LocID>                         
		<Text>A pinched nasal tip refers to a nose that is excessively narrowed in the region of the tip. This type of nasal abnormality can arise as a congenital problem, meaning the patient was born with this or as a result of having had prior unsuccessful rhinoplasty surgery.</Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_NOSETOOHIGH</LocID>                         
		<Text>High Tip of the Nose</Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_NOSETOOHIGH_DESC</LocID>                         
		<Text>The patient's nose is pointed unusually high at the tip.</Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_UNEVEN_NOSTRILS</LocID>                         
		<Text>Uneven Nostrils</Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_UNEVEN_NOSTRILS_DESC</LocID>                         
		<Text>One of the patient's nostrils is of a noticeably different size compared to the other.</Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_BLEPHAROPTOSIS</LocID> <!-- NOT FOR CRP -->                         
		<Text>Blepharoptosis</Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_BLEPHAROPTOSIS_DESC</LocID> <!-- NOT FOR CRP -->                    
		<Text>Blepharoptosis, also known as ptosis, is a drooping of the upper eyelid that may affect one or both eyes. The eyelid may droop only slightly or may droop enough to cover the pupil and block vision.</Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_OCULAR_EXTRUDE</LocID>                         
		<Text>Ocular Contents Extruding from Globe</Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_OCULAR_EXTRUDE_DESC</LocID>                         
		<Text>The patient's eye is extruding the internal contents of the globe of the eye.</Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_OCULAR_MOTILITY</LocID>                         
		<Text>Loss of Ocular Motility</Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_OCULAR_MOTILITY_DESC</LocID>                         
		<Text>Loss of Ocular Motility, also know as Oculomotor Dysfunction, occurs when there is the absence or defect of controlled, voluntary, and purposeful eye movement.</Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_TISSUE_SHRAPNEL</LocID>                         
		<Text>Tissue Shrapnel Damage</Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_TISSUE_SHRAPNEL_DESC</LocID>                         
		<Text>The patient has shallow tissue damage from shrapnel.</Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<!-- ================================================== -->
	<!-- ============= Plastic Surgery v1.0.6 ============= -->
	<!-- ================================================== -->
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_FACE_HEMATOMA</LocID>                         
		<Text>Facial Hematoma</Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_FACE_HEMATOMA_DESC</LocID>                         
		<Text>A facial hematoma is a collection of blood within the face. An injury disrupts the blood vessels so that fluid and blood may collect under the lining.</Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_IMPLANT_INFECTION01</LocID>                         
		<Text>Cheek Implant Infection</Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_IMPLANT_INFECTION01_DESC</LocID>                         
		<Text>The patient has developed an infection around a recent cheek implant. Such an infection is serious and the implant will need to be removed and the wound cleaned.</Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_FAILED_CA01</LocID>                               
		<Text>Failed Cheek Augmentation</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_FAILED_CA01_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>Due to surgery complications, the patient has been unable to have a successful cosmetic surgery outcome. They will not be happy about this. </Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<!--
	Translators, please ignore this:
	Used to quickly add new localisation to the mod 
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>XYZ</LocID>                         
		<Text></Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>XYZ_DESC</LocID>                         
		<Text></Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	-->


	</LocalizedStrings>
	</GameDBStringTable>
</Database>