<Database>
	<!-- Plastic Surgery Mod by Sleepy068 -->
	<GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_EN_ADDON_PLASTICS_TREATMENTS_SURG">
	<LanguageCode>en</LanguageCode>
	<LanguageNameLocalized>English</LanguageNameLocalized>
	<Contributors>
	<Name>Sleepy068</Name>
	</Contributors>

	<LocalizedStrings>
	<!-- =========================================== -->
	<!-- ============= Plastic Surgery ============= -->
	<!-- =========================================== -->
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SUR_SLP_AUGMENTATION_MAMMOPLASTY</LocID>                         
		<Text>Augmentation Mammoplasty</Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SUR_SLP_AUGMENTATION_MAMMOPLASTY_DESC</LocID>                         
		<Text>Breast augmentation is a cosmetic surgery technique using breast-implants and fat-graft mammoplasty techniques to increase the size, change the shape, and alter the texture of the breasts of a woman. \n\nRequired room: Operating room at Plastic Surgery dpt.</Text>	
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SUR_SLP_PLAS_NERVE_DECOM_SURGERY</LocID>                                    	
		<Text>Nerve Reconstructive Surgery</Text>
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SUR_SLP_PLAS_NERVE_DECOM_SURGERY_DESC</LocID>                        	
		<Text>Nerve Reconstructive Surgery, or surgical nerve repair involves exploration of the injured nerve and removal of injured tissue or scar from the nerve endings. After that, a nerve can be directly reconnected if there is enough length on the ends to allow for a good quality repair without tension. \n\nRequired room: Operating room at Neurology dpt.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SUR_SLP_CORRECTIVE_SURGERY</LocID>                                    	
		<Text>Corrective Surgery</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SUR_SLP_CORRECTIVE_SURGERY_DESC</LocID>                        	
		<Text>It is not uncommon for patients to occasionally require corrective surgery, this is carried out to address concerns or complications relating to a previous surgery. Addressing these concerns will help greatly with patient satisfaction at the expense of additional surgery time and further complication risks. \n\nRequired room: Operating room at Plastic Surgery dpt.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SUR_SLP_PLAS_SCAR_REVISION_SURGERY</LocID>                                    	
		<Text>Scar Revision Surgery</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SUR_SLP_PLAS_SCAR_REVISION_SURGERY_DESC</LocID>                        	
		<Text>Scar revision is surgery to improve or reduce the appearance of scars. It also restores function, and corrects skin changes (disfigurement) caused by an injury, wound, poor healing, or previous surgery. \n\nRequired room: Operating room at Plastic Surgery dpt.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SUR_SLP_PLAS_IMPLANT_REMOVAL</LocID>                                    	
		<Text>Breast Implant Removal</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SUR_SLP_PLAS_IMPLANT_REMOVAL_DESC</LocID>                        	
		<Text>Breast implant infections are usually caused by Staphylococcus aureus and coagulase-negative staphylococci. Gram-negative bacilli are rarely reported to be involved in breast implant infections. Although rare, infections of this type generally require the implants to be removed. This surgery removes the breast implants and cleans the tissue around the implants. Follow-up anti-biotic courses are normally required. \n\nRequired room: Operating room at Plastic Surgery dpt.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SUR_SLP_PLAS_CAPSULECTOMY</LocID>                                    	
		<Text>Capsulectomy</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SUR_SLP_PLAS_CAPSULECTOMY_DESC</LocID>                        	
		<Text>Capsulectomy is the surgical removal of scar tissue or capsule that has become thickened and hardened around a breast implant. The capsule is composed of fibroblasts, collagen, and blood vessels. Performing a capsulectomy should alleviate the discomfort and improve the appearance and feel of the patients breasts. \n\nRequired room: Operating room at Plastic Surgery dpt.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SUR_SLP_SAL</LocID>                                    	
		<Text>Suction Assisted Lipectomy (SAL)</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SUR_SLP_SAL_DESC</LocID>                        	
		<Text>Liposuction is invasive surgery that aims to improve the body’s contours and proportion by removing localised and disproportional deposits of fat. Liposuction can remove up to 5 litres of fat with relative safety during one session. Suction Assisted Lipectomy (SAL) is where fat is removed from the body using a vacuum suction. SAL may be dry, wet or tumescent (Tumescent liposuction) depending on the volume of saline (salt solution) which is injected into the operation site before the procedure begins. \n\nRequired room: Operating room at Plastic Surgery dpt.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SUR_SLP_RHINOPLASTY</LocID>                                    	
		<Text>Rhinoplasty</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SUR_SLP_RHINOPLASTY_DESC</LocID>                        	
		<Text>Rhinoplasty, commonly known as a nose job, is a plastic surgery procedure for correcting and reconstructing the nose. There are two types of plastic surgery used – reconstructive surgery that restores the form and functions of the nose and cosmetic surgery that improves the appearance of the nose.  \n\nRequired room: Operating room at Plastic Surgery dpt.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SUR_SLP_PLAS_EYEMSURGERY</LocID>                                    	
		<Text>Eye Muscle Surgery</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SUR_SLP_PLAS_EYEMSURGERY_DESC</LocID>                        	
		<Text>Eye muscle surgery is a surgery to correct strabismus (eye misalignment) or nystagmus (eye wiggling). The surgery involves moving one or more of the eye muscles to adjust the position of the eye or eyes.  \n\nRequired room: Operating room at Plastic Surgery dpt.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SUR_SLP_PLAS_EMERG_REPAIR</LocID>                                    	
		<Text>Emergency Surgery (Plastic)</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SUR_SLP_PLAS_EMERG_REPAIR_DESC</LocID>                        	
		<Text>Emergency Surgery can be defined as surgery that is required to deal with an acute threat to life, organ, limb or tissue caused by external trauma, acute disease process, acute exacerbation of a chronic disease process, or complication of a surgical or other interventional procedure. \n\nImportance: This surgery is considered critical and should be a priority. \n\nRequired room: Operating room at Plastic Surgery dpt.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<!-- Not use yet -->
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SUR_SLP_PLAS_EMERG_EYEREMOVAL</LocID>                                    	
		<Text>Enucleation of the Eye</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<!-- Not use yet -->
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SUR_SLP_PLAS_EMERG_EYEREMOVAL_DESC</LocID>                        	
		<Text>Enucleation is the removal of the eye that leaves the eye muscles and remaining orbital contents intact. This type of ocular surgery is indicated for a number of ocular tumors, in eyes that have suffered severe trauma, and in eyes that are otherwise blind and painful. \n\nRequired room: Operating room at Plastic Surgery dpt.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SUR_SLP_HAIRT</LocID>                                    	
		<Text>Follicular Unit Transplantation</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SUR_SLP_HAIRT_DESC</LocID>                        	
		<Text>Follicular unit extraction, sometimes referred to simply as FUE, is a method of hair transplant surgery that manually removes individual hair follicles from the patient's scalp. Once extracted, hairs are then implanted to bald or thinning areas around the head.  \n\nRequired room: Operating room at Plastic Surgery dpt.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SUR_SLP_PLAS_REPLANT</LocID>                                    	
		<Text>Replantation</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SUR_SLP_PLAS_REPLANT_DESC</LocID>                        	
		<Text>Replantation refers to the surgical reattachment of a body part (such as a finger, hand, or toe) that has been completely cut from the body. The goal of replantation surgery is to reattach and restore function to as much of the injured part as possible.  \n\nRequired room: Operating room at Plastic Surgery dpt.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
    <!-- ==================================================== -->
	<!-- ============= Plastic Surgery vx.x.x.x ============= -->
	<!-- ==================================================== -->
	
	</LocalizedStrings>
	</GameDBStringTable>
</Database>
